<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>    
	<string name="p1"><![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> the butterfly flits around a flower bush looking for the tastiest lunch. <![CDATA[<f>She</f>]]> spies a fresh pink blossom and settles down to drink its nectar.</string>
	<string name="p2"><![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> flutters nearby. <![CDATA[<m>She</m>]]>\'s thirsty too.</string>
	<string name="p3"><![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> notices <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> and wants to join <![CDATA[<f>her</f>]]>, “May I drink from these flowers too?”</string>
	<string name="p4"><![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> answers, “I… I guess so.” <![CDATA[<f>She</f>]]>\'s unsure because the moth looks dangerous.\n<![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> guesses <![CDATA[<f_>her</f_>]]> uncertainty and laughs, “I only look like a wasp. I\'m <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]>, and I like to drink nectar, just like you.”\n<![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> is relieved and makes room to share the flowers.</string>
	<string name="p5"><![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> notices <![CDATA[<f_>her</f_>]]> friend\'s pretty wings. <![CDATA[<f>She</f>]]> says, “Hey, we both have spots on our wings.”\n“And, we both have long antenna,” adds <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]>. They trade compliments as they sip nectar from the flowers.</string>
	<string name="p6">Suddenly a real wasp appears. It is very big, hungry and cranky.\n“I\'m going to eat that butterfly,” it says.</string>
	<string name="p7">“NO!” shouts <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]>, “You will NOT eat my friend.”\nEvery time the wasp lunges at <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]>, <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> moves to stand between them. The wasp shakes its big body and buzzes terrible threats. Bravely, <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> rattles and buzzes right back. Finally, the wasp gives up and leaves.</string>
	<string name="p8">When the real wasp flies away, the friends are so relieved. <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> thanks <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]>, and adds, “That was too much excitement. Maybe we should go somewhere else.”\n<![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> agrees, “Where do you think we should go?”</string>
	<string name="p9">The friends flit and flutter and soon find a bush with bright yellow flowers.\n<![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> says, “I like the color yellow.”\n“Me too,” says <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]>. “But green is my favorite color. Someday I\'m going to be an adventurer and find a rare green flower. What about you?”\n<![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> answers, “I\'ll be the green flower farmer if you bring me one to cultivate.”\nThey drink nectar and daydream together.</string>
	<string name="p10">Finally both are tired and need to go home for dinner.\n“<![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]>, would you like to play again tomorrow?”\n“Yes!” <![CDATA[<m>she</m>]]> answers. The friends make plans to meet tomorrow and say their goodbyes. It has been a wonderful day.</string>
	<string name="p11"><![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> leads the way to <![CDATA[<f_>her</f_>]]> home in a tall tree. <![CDATA[<f>She</f>]]> takes <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> to <![CDATA[<f_>her</f_>]]> room, where there is a cozy bed made of moss. The friends decide to play shop. They make bowls and baubles, and display them on the table.</string>
	<string name="p12"><![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> owns the store, and <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> shops for wooden bowls and other things. <![CDATA[<f>She</f>]]> picks up a mossy sponge and asks, “Is it on sale?” <![CDATA[<f>She</f>]]> tries to haggle with <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> to lower the price, but it\'s priced as marked, $5.\nAfter playing shop, they decide to fly outside.</string>
	<string name="p13">Playing hide and seek, <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> ducks behind a leaf. <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> flies by twice but doesn\'t see <![CDATA[<f>her</f>]]>. On the third pass, <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> giggles which gives <![CDATA[<f>her</f>]]> away, and <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> finds <![CDATA[<f>her</f>]]>.\nAfter playing all afternoon, they have to go home. It has been a fun filled day.</string>
	<string name="p14"><![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> takes <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> to <![CDATA[<m_>her</m_>]]> home, which is nestled under a tree. The room sparkles with lightening bugs and smells of the nectar soup simmering in the kitchen. They each take a bowl of soup and sit down.\n<![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> and <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> trade stories about summer camp. They both liked making animal masks, so they decide to make them again now.</string>
	<string name="p15"><![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> draws a cat with pointy ears, while <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> makes a dog with floppy ears. They cut out holes for the eyes and mouth, and then put the masks on.\n“Meow,” says <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]>.\n“Ruff,” says <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]>.\nThey fly around meowing and barking and laughing until dinnertime. Before parting, they agree to meet at the flower bush again tomorrow. It\'s been a great day.</string>
	<string name="p16">Several butterflies gather around <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]>. They don\'t welcome scary looking wasps.\n<![CDATA[<f_>Her</f_>]]> friend shouts, “You\'re not a butterfly. Go away!”\nThen other butterflies yell, “Go away! You\'re a mean and dangerous wasp!”</string>
	<string name="p17"><![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> is hurt, but instead of leaving, <![CDATA[<m>she</m>]]> explains, “Looking like a wasp is my protection. I\'m a moth, which is a lot like you.”\nA butterfly replies, “But your wings are thin like a wasp. And your antennae don\'t have bulbs at the ends?”\n<![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> stays quiet. “What should I do?” <![CDATA[<f>she</f>]]> wonders.</string>
	<string name="p18">“Hey everybody,” <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> shouts. “I think <![CDATA[<m>she</m>]]>\'s nice. A dangerous wasp wouldn\'t ask.”\n“Thanks,” says <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]>.\n“I\'m sorry about my friends,” whispers <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]>.\n<![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> nods in understanding and forgives. Side by side, they share the flowers.</string>
	<string name="p19">Taking a break from <![CDATA[<m_>her</m_>]]> flower, <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> jokes about <![CDATA[<m_>her</m_>]]> fuzzy antennae. <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> laughs and adds, “Mine have these giant balls.”\n“Let\'s trade,” <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> suggests.\nHaving swapped their gear, they shake their heads. Their antennae swing and bobble and sway with their movements making them laugh even more.</string>
	<string name="p20"><![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> is scared. “Go away,” <![CDATA[<f>she</f>]]> says.\n“But I\'m not a real wasp. I\'m a moth, which is a lot like a butterfly,” <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> explains. \n<![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> doesn\'t believe <![CDATA[<m>her</m>]]>.\nAt first <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> is hurt, but <![CDATA[<m>she</m>]]> decides that <![CDATA[<m>she</m>]]> can find better flowers elsewhere and flutters away.</string>
	<string name="p21">A moment later <![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]> hears buzzing. <![CDATA[<f>She</f>]]> turns and sees a gigantic wasp. It doesn\'t ask to join. It doesn\'t say anything at all. Its mouth is wide-open ready to eat <![CDATA[<f>her</f>]]>!\nAll of the butterflies are so frightened that they fly away as fast as they can.</string>
	<string name="p22">The wasp has the flower bush all to itself. It drinks a little nectar to quench its thirst, but it\'s still hungry. Seeing nothing good to eat, it departs.</string>
	<string name="p23">The flower bush is quiet and warm in the sun. <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> flutters by and notices that all the butterflies are gone. The flowers are still juicy, so <![CDATA[<m>she</m>]]> stops. The nectar is delicious.</string>

	<string name="optionyes">Yes</string>
	<string name="optionno">No</string>
	<string name="optionbush">Oleander Bush</string>
	<string name="optionflutterbys"><![CDATA[<f>Flutterby</f>]]>\'s</string>
	<string name="optionmarguerites"><![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]>\'s</string>
	
	<string name="optionjoin">Ask <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> to stay</string>
	<string name="optionleave">Tell <![CDATA[<m>Marguerite</m>]]> to go</string>
	
</resources>
